♪
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA] Why do I want to
change my life?
To help me find a place
at school?
♪
[gasps]
[UKA]
That is part of it.
But more than that...
♪
[sighs]
[gasps]
♪
SPARKLE 1 BECAUSE I MET YOU
[FEMALE STUDENT 1A]
Good morning!
You manage to get
the English homework done?
[FEMALE STUDENT 1B] Passed out
barely halfway through!
[sighs]
[yawns]
Morning.
What's up?
Hey there, Kai!
[SATORU] [chuckles]
Morning!
Really? More lemon soda today?
[TOMOYA] That's all you've been
drinking lately.
[KAI]
So? They're good.
[AYUMI] Hmm?
Maybe I should try it!
Where do you normally
pick it up?
-[MALE STUDENT 1A] Yo, Miura!
-Huh?
[MALE STUDENT 1A] Aren't you
a little standoffish?
[MALE STUDENT 1B] I don't like
how many looks you're getting.
[MALE STUDENT 1A]
You should go home
and dye your hair
a normal color.
Hmm.
-What?
-You wanna go?
[MALE STUDENT 1B] Wait.
You know you're not supposed
to shake those.
Whoa, chill out!
[all gasp
[screams]
[MALE STUDENT 1A]
That's gotta sting!
-[KAI] Oh.
-Well, good luck with that!
[AYUMI]
What'd you do that for, Kai?
[KAI]
What? They annoyed me.
Their fault for dodging.
Take a little responsibility!
Hey, are you okay?
Someone needs
to get this girl a towel!
[MALE STUDENT 1C]
Not my problem!
[FEMALE STUDENT 1C]
No?
[UKA] Whoa.
Someone's talking to me.
She's worried about me!
-[UKA]What am I supposed to do?
-[AYUMI] You apologize to her
this instant, Kai!
[indistinct chatter]
That's my bad.
[SATORU] Try to sound
like you mean it.
Sorry about him.
Doesn't even realize
he's being a jerk.
[UKA]
He's looking at me.
Miura is staring
straight at me!
I'm so sorry!
[AYUMI]
Why are you sorry?
[SATORU] Why do I feel like
I've seen her somewhere before?
That's Uka Ishimori.
She's in our class!
[SATORU] What?
You're kidding me!
Different vibe
from the rest of us, right?
Hmm.
[UKA] School's always
been difficult for me.
I haven't made many
good memories.
I had a nickname
in junior high, "Stony."
[junior high bully chuckles]
[FEMALE JUNIOR HIGH BULLY 1A]
There's just something
-I don't like about her.
-[BULLY] Why doesn't she leave?
[UKA] It seems like
I bother everyone.
But if I had to get splashed,
I'd rather it be Miura
than someone else.
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA]
Is that weird?
-I'm caught up!
-[ASUMI] Where'd you get that
-lipstick?
-Pretty good episode!
-[YURU] I'll take you!
-[UKA] I made up my mind.
I want to have more fun
than I did back then.
Though, I don't think
I've made progress.
[ABE]
Everyone!
Go back to your seats,
so our Day Leader
can get our class off
to a good start.
All rise.
[UKA]
Please, Mister Abe.
I know I'm wearing
my gym clothes.
I'm begging you to not point
it out to everyone.
[ABE] Wait.
Why are you in gym clothes?
Well, Mister Miura?
[indistinct chatter]
Hold on. You too, Ishimori?
Oh. I can explain, sir.
-[KAI] We got soda on us.
-[gasps]
Good grief. Wasted no time
causing trouble!
[TONBO]
Aw, c'mon, man!
-[Tonbo chuckles]
-[MARIN] You good, Kai?
-[ABE] Anyway...
-[UKA] But wait.
-it's time to get on with
class. -[UKA] If it got on him,
-I didn't see it.
-[ABE] Fine.
[UKA]
He wasn't in my junior high.
Actually, I doubt he even
remembers the time
we met before high school.
It was winter.
And his hair reminded me
of lemon soda.
It woke me up.
♪
Hey, Mom and Dad.
Hi, honey!
Everything go all right
at school?
[UKA]
Today was fun.
That's great.
Glad to hear it!
You'll have to bring your new
friends over sometime soon!
[UKA]
Oh, sure.
I can always tell when I see
a kid from your school
riding the train.
Not very subtle over there.
[UKA'S DAD]
If you felt like it,
it's not too late
to transfer...
I'm exactly where I want to be!
Okay, then.
[UKA] My parents
are overprotective of me.
I feel like I can't do anything
for myself.
But that's my fault.
They spoil me, but I let them.
Still...
I won't let things stay
like this anymore.
Yeah!
Starting tomorrow!
[birds chirping]
I got too excited,
and arrived super early.
But I'll make the best of it!
Good mor...
[UKA]
My voice just cracked.
I'll try louder!
-Good morning!
-[KAI] Huh?
[gasps]
[UKA]
Kill me.
Morning.
[gasps]
[KAI]
What, ignoring me?
[gasps]
Kinda early
for the cold shoulder.
No! I'm not!
Right. Then repeat after me.
[KAI]
"Good."
Good.
-[KAI] "Mor."
-Mor.
-[KAI] "Ning."
-Ning.
[KAI]
Got it?
Sorry, uh! Good morning!
[sighs]
Morning.
[UKA]
Good morning.
[cellphone vibrates]
-[KAI] What? I'm already here.
-[UKA] He said it.
-[UKA] He said it to me!
-Nothin' much.
I just woke up early.
Satoru? Grab me a lemon soda
on your way.
[UKA] No one's here.
Just him and me!
Endou, answer this one.
What? How am I supposed
to solve that?
[MIZOGUCHI]
By listening.
Stay after school
and you'll learn.
You think I don't have
anything better to do?
[MIZOGUCHI] [sighs] Then,
ask a friend for the answer.
Like any of them know
[Ayumi screams]
[AYUMI] I need someone
to save me, quick!
[UKA] Hold on.
I know this one!
Hey, are you doing okay?
-[AYUMI] I don't wanna stay
late! -[UKA] Should I?
What if trying to help
makes things worse?
[AYUMI]...screwed if I can't
get a hand from someone.
-[UKA] We're not friends.
-[AYUMI] Hey, teach,
you wouldn't really do this
to me, would you?
[UKA]
But...
-Here, look at mine!
-Huh?
[AYUMI]
You have the answer?
[gasps]
Huh?
"Ten by the root of two minus
two by the root
of three over three."
-[MIZOGUCHI] Correct.
[TONBO] Whoa, incredible.
[YURU] I can't believe
she knew that!
[MARIN]
Huh? I zoned out.
[MIZOGUCHI] All right.
Settle down, kids.
Let's move on.
[UKA] They're talking,
but not in a bad way.
They're actually
complimenting me.
I can't believe it.
[indistinct chatter]
[AYUMI]
Hey, Ishimori!
My name's Ayumi Endou!
Thanks again!
You really saved me!
Oh, it's no problem!
[SATORU] Hey!
Come on! Time to go!
[AYUMI]
Ah, you're right!
You wanna come with us?
Huh?
Oh. Is that a no?
Sorry! Yeah!
[chuckles]
[AYUMI]
Well, hurry up!
Right. Sure thing!
[UKA]
Did I make a friend? Already?
[REMI]
Wow, is that Stony?
[REMI'S FEMALE FRIEND]
No way!
I thought she was gonna go
to Shinsei High.
Yeah, wasn't she?
Think she failed the exam?
But the only good thing
about Stony's her brains!
-"Stony?"
-That's the nickname
everyone called her
in Junior High.
For real?
Yeah, just look at her!
I mean, she's slow
and doesn't talk.
[REMI] And all she does is
stare at people
with a blank face.
There's no better name!
Not for a freak like that!
[REMI'S MALE FRIEND]
True, true!
Old Stony can barely
even blink!
[all laughing]
[REMI'S MALE FRIEND] Look
at her, just standing there!
[REMI'S FEMALE FRIEND]
Right? We couldn't
move her if we tried.
[REMI'S MALE FRIEND]
For real!
Hey! Don't listen to them!
[REMI'S FEMALE FRIEND]
The stone's running!
[laughs]
No way!
Let's leave.
[REMI'S FEMALE FRIEND]
Yeah, I'm bored.
Did someone call in
the butthead brigade?
Like for real for real.
So I guess Ishimori failed
the Shinsei test?
[SATORU]
There's always a chance,
she wanted to come here,
ya know.
[TOMOYA]
Oh, come on.
This place is just
a backup school.
Who'd choose to come here?
[UKA] I shouldn't have thought
things were getting better.
I'm Stony.
Now and forever.
But, wait.
If I think like that,
my life will never change.
[indistinct chatter]
You guys, anyone see
where Kai ran off to?
No. Not me.
[indistinct chatter]
Hmm.
♪
I HAVE TO CHANGE
[KAI] You can't just
tell yourself to change.
All you're doing is putting
pressure on yourself.
Writing it like that
makes it look like a curse.
[UKA]
What's Miura doing here?
Why is he in the library?
[KAI]
Aw, c'mon.
[UKA]
I'm sorry!
[KAI]
Don't apologize!
I'm sor...
[UKA]
I'm here.
I actually go to the same
school as him now.
But I'm still acting
like a doormat.
I'm hopeless.
[Remi's female friend laughs]
[REMI'S FEMALE FRIEND] I got
Stony's shoes from her locker!
[REMI'S MALE FRIEND] I swear,
you're always doing this!
[REMI]
No kidding.
[panting]
Well, if anyone deserves it,
it's Stony.
Yeah, fine.
[REMI'S MALE FRIEND]
You jerk.
Don't come crying to me
if you get in trouble.
[REMI'S FEMALE FRIEND]
I think I'll be fine.
As if she'd ever say anything!
[Remi's male friend chuckles]
♪
[UKA] It's not like this is
anything new to me.
It doesn't bother me anymore.
If I let myself care,
it'll hurt more.
But if I harden my heart
like a stone, then I'll...
-[KAI] React, damn it!
-[gasps]
Go find someone.
Ask for help.
But who?
Huh?
[UKA] Why wasn't I able
to pass the Shinsei test?
School would've been peaceful
without stuff like this, but...
[whimpering]
He told me.
♪
[MALE TEACHER 1A] You have
nothing to worry about.
Considering how high
her grades are,
I can't imagine she'll have
trouble getting into Shinsei.
That's great news!
Thank goodness!
And I can't say that about
any other student going here,
but your daughter is
a special case.
[UKA'S MOM] Oh.
Her friends won't be there?
So, dear, what do you think?
[UKA]
It's not about where I am.
I need to change who I am.
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA] Still, I wanted to go
to Hachimitsu High.
[REMI'S FEMALE FRIEND]
Wait, that's crazy!
[REMI]
Right? Isn't it, though?
Oh, my bad. Whoops. Wait.
Would ya look at that.
It's Stony!
[REMI'S FEMALE FRIEND]
Oh! You're right!
[REMI] Yuck! Can't believe
we have to see her in the wild.
[REMI'S MALE FRIEND]
Going to Shinsei?
[REMI'S FEMALE FRIEND]
That's rich!
Perfect for a dweeb like her!
[REMI] The uniforms
are almost as ugly as her.
[REMI'S MALE FRIEND] [laughs]
Let's go.
I just tried a new facial
-cleanser from that shop...
-Yeah.
[REMI]
See ya, Stony!
[indistinct chatter]
[gasps]
[UKA]
Lemon soda.
♪
Hmm.
[UKA]
I'm okay.
[KAI]
This one.
This would suit you
unexpectedly well.
Well, it's good enough
for me, at least.
[whimpering]
[KAI'S MALE FRIEND 1A]
Yo, Kai!
[KAI]
Here.
♪
[KAI'S MALE FRIEND 1A]
You know her?
[KAI]
Nope. No clue.
-[KAI'S MALE FRIEND 1B] Huh?
-[KAI'S MALE FRIEND 1C] Hmm?
[UKA]
A boy I'd never met.
And he was so beautiful.
[weeping]
[UKA]
For some reason, I froze up.
I couldn't move my hand.
And because of that, I had
no choice but to come here.
He doesn't remember that day.
Why would he?
It meant nothing to him.
-[TONBO] Kai!
-Huh?
-[TONBO] You're late.
-[KAI] Yeah.
Overslept?
Woke up like normal, thank you.
Then what?
Care to explain why you didn't
get back to us?
[MIRU] You didn't even read
our messages.
[UKA] But to me,
it meant everything.
♪
[Uka panting]
[UKA] I know I can do this.
I have to!
[REMI'S MALE FRIEND]
Ishimori,
hear my stomach growling?
Go buy us some food, m'kay?
[REMI'S MALE FRIEND] You can
grab me a sausage roll.
Hurry up. Don't make us wait.
Oh? What's this?
Huh?
[fizzing]
[all screaming]
-What in the world?
-I cannot believe
you're that gross!
[REMI'S MALE FRIEND] Hey.
You got a screw loose? Huh?
[groans]
[whimpering]
[KAI] Look at the cool kids.
Somethin' wrong?
[gasps]
You good?
[REMI'S MALE FRIEND]
What do you think?
C'mon. Say it. Like I said.
-Huh?
-[KAI] Go find someone.
Ask for help.
[UKA]
But who?
[KAI]
Me.
[gasps]
[KAI]
Good grief. This again?
After me. "Will you."
Will you.
[KAI]
"Please."
Please.
[KAI]
"Help."
Help.
[KAI]
"Me."
Help me.
[sniffles]
Will you please help me?
[Kai chuckles]
Now that wasn't so hard.
[KAI]
Hey. Short, Dumb, and Ugly.
[ALL]
Huh?
[KAI]
You try to mess with her again,
you'll be answering to me.
-Excuse me?
-Whatever, man!
Jerk! Friggin' white knight!
[REMI'S FEMALE FRIEND]
What a piece of crap!
-Who does he think he is?
-Forget it! Screw that guy!
[weeping]
[KAI] Get up.
Get off the ground!
If you're gonna cry,
at least find somewhere better.
You're in the way.
Just like on the sidewalk.
[gasps]
♪
This would suit you
unexpectedly well.
[UKA] Ever since then, to me,
Miura was like the sun.
[KAI'S MALE FRIEND]
You know her?
[KAI]
Nope. No clue.
[KAI'S MALE FRIEND 1B]
Let's go!
[UKA]
I want to change.
[sighs]
[crying]
[UKA]
I'm sorry.
Come on, stop that!
Huh?
[chuckles]
[UKA]
For Uka Ishimori,
in the spring of her
freshman year?
-[chuckles]
-[UKA] Her curse is no more.
Broken by that lemon soda.
TO BE CONTINUED